我们 是水晶
♪ We ♪ are the crystal
战士
♪ gems
我们总能拯救世界
♪ we'll always save the day
如果你认为我们不行
♪ and if you think we can't, ♪
我们总能找到方法
♪ we'll always find a way
这就是为什么这个世界
♪ that's why the people
的人
♪ of this world
相信
♪ believe in
石榴
♪ Garnet
紫晶
♪ Amethyst
和珍珠
♪ and Pearl
和史蒂文!
and Steven!
我是
我妈
欢迎关注微博@UUU字幕组，获取最新熟肉信息！
出品
UUU字幕组
翻译
SG
校对
Husky
特效
presisco
压制
紧急情况!
This is an emergency!
为什么母星势力要在路上窃走人类?
Why is Homeworld stealing humans from the boardwalk?
我不知道, 但她们只带走我的朋友!
I don't know, but they're only taking my friends!
她们甚至带走了康妮!
They even got Connie!
如果我们不做点什么
If we don't do something,
那些宝石会把他们带进太空!
they're going to take them into space!
而我们的飞船被抢走了, 所以如果他们离开了地球...
And our spaceship got jacked, so if they leave Earth...
就再也回不来了
They'll be gone for good.
呃啊! 她们是什么人啊?
Ugh! Who were these guys?
那个我之前见过的小宝石, 她叫海蓝宝
That little gem I saw before, her name's Aquamarine.
什么? !
What?!
她还带了个大家伙--一个叫托帕石的融合体
She's got a big friend -- a fusion, named Topaz.
一个托帕石融合体和一个海蓝宝?
A topaz fusion and an aquamarine?
她们很厉害吗?
Are they a big deal?
当然了!
Uh, yes!
蓝钻和黄钻肯定是亲自派遣他们来的
Blue and Yellow Diamond must have sent them personally.
钻石们? 哦不
The Diamonds? Oh, no.
她们一定在是为动物园收集更多的人类!
They must be collecting more humans for the zoo!
但地球上有许多人类
But there's loads of humans on Earth.
为什么他们只抓走你的朋友?
Why are they only grabbing your friends?
也许因为...我的朋友最棒了!
Maybe...because my friends are the best!
康妮发来的!
It's from Connie!
我知道他们在哪里了!
I know where they are!
保持警惕, 他们可能在任何地方
Stay alert. They could be anywhere.
康妮发给你更多的照片了吗?
Did Connie send you any more pictures?
不, 没有
No, nothing.
我们知道他们就在这里
We know they're here somewhere.
康妮? 拉尔斯?
Connie? Lars?
莎蒂?
Sadie?
洋葱头?
Onion?
为什么是他们?
Why them?
那-那是康妮的手机...
W-Was that Connie's pho--
啊 糟了~
Oh, no!
你找到我们了
You found us.
救命!
Help!
放弃吧海蓝宝!
Give it up, Aquamarine!
你已经无处可逃了!
There's nowhere to run!
哦 你说什么?
Oh, what's this, now?
你以为我们正在逃跑吗?
Did you think we were running away?
史蒂文, 你快逃吧...不过先救救我们!
Steven, save yourself... after you save us!
你知道吗, 仔细想想
You know, now that I think about it,
这个史蒂文似乎知道名单上的所有人
this Steven does seem to know everyone on our list.
而名单也是由一个史蒂文提供的
The list did come from a Steven, after all.
或许你可以帮我解决问题
Maybe you can help us out.
放开那些人类!
Just let the humans go!
呃 才不要
Uh, no.
这些傻瓜是谁?
Who are these dullards?
我们是水晶宝石战队! 你个呆瓜!
We're the Crystal Gems, you chump!
是啊 是啊
Yeah, yeah.
玫瑰石英的老奴仆们
Rose Quartz's old lackeys.
这也在报告中
That was in the report, too.
我们来不是为了你们这些无赖宝石的
We're not here for any of you rogue gems.
我们会把你们完全放在一旁
We'll leave you totally alone...
只要...
if...
你们告诉我哪里可以找到我爸爸
you tell us where we can find my dad.
我不知道你在说什么!
I don't know what you're talking about!
我们来瞧瞧
Let's see.
黄钻让我带回, 呃, 我爸爸
Yellow Diamond asked for, uh, my dad,
一个康妮,, 一个拉尔斯, 一个莎蒂, 一个快递员
a Connie, a Lars, a Sadie, a mailman,
我想还有一个洋葱
and an onion, I think.
六种人类
Six human variations
由橄榄石5XG号的报告指定
specified in a report by Peridot 5XG.
啊不, 这里有很多人类
Oh, no, there's lots of humans.
有我爸爸, 康妮, 拉尔斯和莎蒂
There's my dad, Connie, Lars and Sadie,
邮递员, 我想还有洋葱
the mailman, onion... I think.
名单
The list.
是我把名单给他们的
I gave them the list.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
海蓝宝没有爸爸
Aquamarine doesn't have a dad.
她在找一个叫"我爸爸"的人!
She's looking for someone named "my dad!"
这都是我的错
This is all my fault.
现在别担心这个了
Don't worry about that now.
我们的目的还是没变--击败宝石
Our objective's still the same -- beat the gems...
拯救伙伴!
Save our friends!
嘿, 托帕石, 看啊
Hey, Topaz, look!
她们又想再输掉一场对战
They want to lose another fight.
不, 石榴, 我已经移情别恋了, 我发誓!
No, Garnet, I've moved on, I swear!
石榴!
Garnet!
这很卑鄙啊!
That's dirty!
我的矛可以在不伤害到人类的情况下击中她
My spear can reach her without hurting the hostages.
哦, 那你可真棒棒
Oh, you're so smart.
再 见!
Goodbye!
这越来越烦了
This is getting annoying.
嘿, 托帕石, 你能帮我回忆一下吗?
Hey, Topaz, can you remind me?
当然了 我的记忆力非常好
I mean, my memory is perfect,
但是 我们得到的指令是带回六个人类
but our orders were to bring back these six humans.
我只是不太确定
I'm just not sure.
她们指明要...活的吗?
Did they specify... alive?
你知道吗, 我想她们没有这么要求呢
You know, I don't think they did.
杰米
Jamie.
史蒂文?
Steven?
我只是在想
I just think,
如果你那么关心你的这些朋友们
if you care about your friends or whatever,
你就该告诉我爸爸在哪里
you should tell me where my dad is,
好吗?
all right?
我们该怎么办? !
What are we going to do?!
史蒂文!
Steven!
停下!
Stop!
我知道你们可以在哪里找到我爸爸
I know where you can find my dad.
噢!
Ooh!
在哪? 在哪?!
Where? Where?!
就在这里
Right here.
我就是你们一直在找的人
I'm the one you're looking for.
我就是我爸爸!
I am my dad!
-什么? -啥?
What? Huh?
我知道你在想什么, 托帕石
I know what you're thinking, Topaz.
虽然史蒂文就是我爸爸有点可疑
It seems a little suspicious that my dad is also a Steven.
但你知道吗...
But you know...
如果这意味着我们能离开这儿, 我也就信了
if it means getting out of here, I'll believe it.
史蒂文!
Steven!
史蒂文, 你知道你在做什么吗?
Steven, do you know what you're doing?
噢! 嗨, 拉尔斯
Oh! Hi, Lars.
别担心, 我会用我的泡泡把我们都炸出去
Don't worry, I'm gonna bust us all out with my bubble power!
她身体好厚实
Her body's so thick.
这可能有点困难
This might be a little difficult.
是时候走了
Time to go.
呃, 史蒂文, 你
Uh, Steven, di--
你有什么具体的计划或...
did you actually have a plan or --
再给我一点时间...
Just need a minute...
真高兴见到你们
Very nice meeting you all,
你们的服从真让我欣赏, 不过...
and your compliance is appreciated, but...
我们在这的任务完成了, 那么...
our job here is done, so...
我们赶快回母星吧
Let's get back to Homeworld already.
可我已经在自己的"母星"了
But I'm already on my home world.
我今天的邮件还没派送呢
I haven't even delivered all the mail today.
别担心 我能做到的
Don't worry. I can do this.
哦! 你得抓紧时间了史蒂文
Ohh! You might want to hurry, Steven.
这黄色泥潭之中死神的威胁
The threat of us perishing in this quagmire of yellow
感觉是相当真实的--
feels very real --
包裹在四周的那种真实
a real encompassing kind of real.
像霓虹色的死亡陷阱 此般紧绷着禁锢我们
A neon death trap, which has imprisoned us so tightly,
如长袖冗余的冬衣
like a winter coat that's too big in the sleeves.
拉尔斯 停下! 我得集中注意力!
Lars, stop! I need to concentrate!
呃
Ugh.
就算以后再也不让我来地球了
If I never get sent on another mission to Earth,
我也不会心怀感激的
it'll be too soon.
简直严刑拷打我哦
What an ordeal.
但是钻石们需要我
But the Diamonds needed me.
这就是作为精英的包袱啊
That's the burden of being the best.
纠缠的图样之中又有何种正义存在呢?
What justice is there in such a gross tangling of symbols?!
能不能安静点?! 坏了我好心情!
Will you stop?! You're ruining my moment!
史蒂文
Steven.
我马上就好!
I almost got it!
哈?
Huh?
啥? 托帕石!
What? Topaz!
收拾一下这个烂摊子
Get this mess cleaned up.
你 托帕石 帮帮她
And, Topaz, help her out.
我在设定路线
I'm setting a course.
门!
The door!
哈?
Huh?
拉尔斯!
Lars!
拉尔斯?!
Lars?!
史蒂文 咱们融合吧!
Steven, let's fuse!
我们已经升空了
We're already in the air.
现在该怎么回去呢?
How are we going to get back?
小心!
Watch out!
在出大气层之前你们能做个了断
I'd really appreciate you wrapping it up down there
我就谢天谢地了
before we exit the atmosphere.
快 拉尔斯 你得站起来啊!
Come on! Lars, you gotta get up!
我们得快跑了!
We gotta move!
哇!
Whoa!
哦! 拉尔斯!
Oh! Lars!
来帮帮我啊!
Come on! Help me!
拉尔斯!
Lars!
拉尔斯
Lars.
谢谢! 快去门那儿
Hey, thanks! Get to the door!
托帕石! 使点劲做个了断好不好!
Topaz, pull it together and finish this!
史蒂文?
Steven?
康妮 我很抱歉!
Connie, I'm sorry!
你在说什么?!
What are you talking about?!
你被抓走都是我的错...
It's my fault you were abducted...
都怪我大家被抓去
why everyone was taken.
如果不是因为我
If it weren't for me,
钻石们也不会来抓我的朋友们
the diamonds wouldn't have come for my friends.
如果不是因为我妈妈
If it weren't for my mom,
她们也不会想要摧毁地球!
they wouldn't even be trying to destroy the Earth!
史蒂文!
Steven!
集中注意!
Focus!
现在又怎么了?
What now?
-去门那儿 -好
-The door. -Right.
紫翠玉!
Alexandrite!
把我们带到水面上 我们要跳下去!
Take us close to the water. We're gonna jump!
-什么? ! -哈?
-What?! -Huh?
好了
Okay.
呃 走! 快走!
Uh, go! Go.
史蒂文! 我好像被吓瘫了
Steven, I-I seem to be paralyzed with fear.
哇!
Whoa!
勇气可嘉
Nice try.
但是别抱希望了 我爸爸
But it's hopeless, my dad.
我可不能空手回去
I can't go back to Homeworld
钻石们会失望的
without getting what the Diamonds want.
我...不是我爸爸
I'm...not my dad.
什么?
What?
我不是我爸爸!
I'm not my dad!
这任务还要浪费我多少时间啊?
How much longer is this mission going to take?
我能现在就结束你的任务
Well, I can end it for you right now.
哦 是吗?
Oh, really?
我在所有人类之中
I'm someone the Diamonds will want
是钻石们最想要的那个--
more than any of these humans --
水晶宝石反叛军的领袖--
the leader of the Crystal Gem rebellion --
粉碎了粉钻的那颗宝石
the gem that shattered Pink Diamond.
我不是我爸爸
I'm not my dad.
我是我妈妈
I'm my mom.
我是玫瑰石英!
I'm Rose Quartz!
不可能
No way.
史蒂文?
Steven?
不 别啊 史蒂文!
No. Don't! Steven!
你在干嘛? !
What are you doing?!
我明白了
I get it now.
只有我能终止我妈妈挑起的事端
I'm the only one who can stop what she started.
我能把所有事画上句号!
I can stop all of it!
你错了! 史蒂文 马上下来!
You're wrong! Steven, get down here!
她肯定不想我这么做
She wouldn't have wanted this.
但是我想
But I do.
如果你还不下来
I'm gonna kick your butt
我肯定要狠狠踢你屁股!
if you don't come down here right now!
史蒂文
Steven.
不 你别想!
No! Don't you dare!
我爱你们
I love you.
不!
No!
停下!
Stop!
史蒂文!
Steven!